- ObjectiveID: 09A_M1_EnterZone_EG
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M1_EG_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Morgaine_WC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M1
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 09A_M1_Flask
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M1_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M1_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M1_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M1_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M1_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M1_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M1_EnterZone_SM
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M1_SM_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Morgaine_WC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M1
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 09A_M1_Flask
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M1_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M1_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M1_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M1_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M1_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M1_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M1_EnterZone_RW
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M1_RW_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Morgaine_WC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M1
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 09A_M1_Flask
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M1_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M1_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M1_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M1_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M1_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M1_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M2_FindOakes
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M2_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Morgaine_WC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M2
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M1
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M2_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionFamilyWardAngryEarthT4
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M2_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M2_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M2_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M2_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M2_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M2_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M3_EnterJungle
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M3_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Hargest_NE_C
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M3
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M2
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M3_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 2.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M3_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M3_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M3_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M3_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M3_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M3_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M4_ReachSettlement
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M4_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Riches_M5
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M4
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M3
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M4_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M4_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M4_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M4_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M4_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M4_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M4_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M5_DefendSettlement
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M5_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Riches_M5
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M5
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M4
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M5_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M5_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M5_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M5_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M5_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M5_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M5_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M6_FindKim
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M6_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Kim
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M6
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M5
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M6_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 2.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M6_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M6_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M6_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M6_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M6_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M6_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M7_ExtractKim
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M7_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Kim_SC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M7
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M6
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M7_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M7_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M7_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M7_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M7_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M7_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M7_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M8_MeetTaurus
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M8_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Taurus
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M8
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M7
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M8_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 4.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M8_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M8_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M8_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M8_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M8_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M8_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M9_MeetShirzad
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M9_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Shirzad
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M9
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M8
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M9_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 2.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M9_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M9_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M9_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M9_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M9_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M9_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M10_MeetKurok
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M10_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Kurok
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M10
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M9
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M10_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: BananaT1
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M10_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M10_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M10_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M10_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M10_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M10_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M11_FightMahantaram
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M11_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Morgaine_WC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M11
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M10
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M11_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: 09A_M11_CraftingMatsBox
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M11_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M11_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M11_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M11_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M11_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M11_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M12_FightMedusa
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M12_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Trahern_HG
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M12
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M11
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M12_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M12_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M12_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M12_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M12_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M12_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M12_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M13_AttuneStaff
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M13_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Morgaine_SE
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M13
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M12
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M13_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 4.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M13_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M13_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M13_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M13_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M13_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M13_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M14_GetInfusedSeed
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M14_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Morgaine_LC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M14
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M13
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M14_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M14_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M14_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M14_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M14_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M14_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M14_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_M15_FightArtemis
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_M15_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Trahern_End
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_M15
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M14
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_M15_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: Artifact_Set1_MediumLegs
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@09A_M15_Title"
  Description: "@09A_M15_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M15_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_M15_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_M15_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_M15_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S0_SecretoftheSpores
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S0_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Eldred
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S0
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M1
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S0_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: SporeJellyT1
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S0_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S0_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S0_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S0_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S0_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S0_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S1_SaveAnimals
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S1_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Murrow_WC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S1
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M1
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S1_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: BeastSporesT1
  ItemRewardQty: 20.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S1_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S1_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S1_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S1_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S1_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S1_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S3_HuntHercyne
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S3_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Vachon_WC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S3
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M1
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S3_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S3_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S3_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S3_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S3_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S3_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S3_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S4_BlowUpFarm
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S4_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S4
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M3
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S4_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: AngryEarthSporesT1
  ItemRewardQty: 20.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S4_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S4_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S4_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S4_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S4_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S4_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S5_SavePrivateer
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S5_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_James
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S5
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M4
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S5_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S5_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S5_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S5_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S5_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S5_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S5_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S6_TrackBeasts
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S6_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Fionn
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S6
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M5
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S6_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S6_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S6_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S6_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S6_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S6_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S6_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S7_StopPlague
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S7_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Ramla
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S7
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M5
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S7_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: AncientSporesT1
  ItemRewardQty: 20.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S7_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S7_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S7_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S7_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S7_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S7_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S8_FixAncientWiring
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S8_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Josephine
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S8_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S8_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S8_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S8_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S8_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S8_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S8_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S9_HackDefenses
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S9_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Kievan
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S9
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_S7
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S9_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PetrifiedFragmentsT1
  ItemRewardQty: 20.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S9_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S9_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S9_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S9_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S9_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S9_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S10_FindTaurusRelics
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S10_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Marwa
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S10
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M7
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S10_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: BeastSporesT1
  ItemRewardQty: 20.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S10_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S10_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S10_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S10_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S10_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S10_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S11_BeatTimeTrial
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S11_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Marwa_HHOP
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S11
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S11_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S11_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S11_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S11_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S11_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S11_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S11_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S12_TraverseLionCave
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S12_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Shirzad
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S12
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S12_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S12_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S12_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S12_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S12_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S12_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S12_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S13_FightLizardAvatar
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S13_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Barug
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S13
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S13_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S13_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S13_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S13_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S13_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S13_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S13_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S14_FightEliteBeasts
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S14_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Manmosu_SD
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S14
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S14_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S14_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S14_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S14_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S14_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S14_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S14_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S15_ResearchDarkMagic
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S15_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Johannes
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S15
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S15_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: UnpetrifiedFleshT1
  ItemRewardQty: 20.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S15_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S15_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S15_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S15_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S15_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S15_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S16_DestroyAbomination
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S16_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Johannes
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S16
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S16_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PetrifiedFragmentsT1
  ItemRewardQty: 20.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S16_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S16_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S16_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S16_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S16_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S16_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S17_EstablishDefenses
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S17_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Hargest_LC
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S17
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M14
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S17_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: AngryEarthSporesT1
  ItemRewardQty: 20.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S17_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S17_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S17_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S17_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S17_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S17_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S18_ScanElafryMagic
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S18_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Gauss
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S18
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M15
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S18_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 4.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S18_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S18_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S18_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S18_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S18_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S18_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S19_DestroyBadPlants
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S19_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Trahern_SD
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S19
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_S14
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S19_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S19_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S19_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S19_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S19_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S19_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S19_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S20_DefeatBeastLords
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S20_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_Manmosu_SD
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S20
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_S14
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S20_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S20_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S20_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S20_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S20_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S20_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S20_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 09A_S21_AmongStatues
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: null
  CanBeShared: null
  CanFastTravel: null
  Task: 09A_S21_Container_Main
  NpcDestinationId: 09a_EdithShackleton_end
  ExclusiveTerritory: null
  AchievementId: 09A_S8
  RequiredAchievementId: 09A_M11
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: 60.0
  SuccessGameEventId: 09A_S21_Success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: GypsumOrb
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: "@09A_S21_Title"
  Description: "@09A_S21_Description"
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_S21_Prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@09A_S21_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@09A_S21_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@09A_S21_Completed"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_objective
  Type: Mission
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: true
  CanBeShared: true
  CanFastTravel: false
  Task: FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Marauder_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: 9.0
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: 1.0
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: ""
  Description: ""
  PlayerPrompt: ""
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: ""
  InProgressResponse: ""
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: ""
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: ""
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_objective
  Type: Mission
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: true
  CanBeShared: true
  CanFastTravel: false
  Task: FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Syndicate_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: 9.0
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: 1.0
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: ""
  Description: ""
  PlayerPrompt: ""
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: ""
  InProgressResponse: ""
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: ""
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: ""
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_objective
  Type: Mission
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: null
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: true
  CanBeShared: true
  CanFastTravel: false
  Task: FM_R09_PVP_ControlSpot_Covenant_container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: 9.0
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: null
  SuccessGameEventId: ""
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: 1.0
  CanBeAbandoned: true
  Title: ""
  Description: ""
  PlayerPrompt: ""
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: ""
  InProgressResponse: ""
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: ""
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: ""
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: ""
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
